A Guide to the Virginia Intercollegiate Association Papers 1954-1969
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Administrative Correspondence
  - Subject Schools Correspondence
    - Member Schools Roster 1957-1964 (Box-folder 8:2)
    - Memoradum ( Member Schools) 1957-1958 June (Box-folder 8:3)
    - Memoranda 1959-1960 (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Memoranda 1958-1959 (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Memoranda 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Memoranda 1962-1963 (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Memoranda 1956 January/June (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Memorandum 1965 July/December (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Memorandums 1957 January/October (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Memorandums 1963, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 8:11)
    - Memorandums 1967-1968 (Box-folder 8:12)
    - Memorandums Campus 1965-1966 (Box-folder 8:13)
    - VIA Coaches Conferences 1955-1959 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - VIA Correspondence (Group I) 1954-1957 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - District (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Directory 1954 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Eastern District Conference 1957-1967 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Group II (minutes) 1959-1960 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Meetings (Group II) 1960-1967 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Member School 1954 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Member School 1963-1968 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Minutes (Group II) 1954-1955 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Minutes (Group III) 1954-1958 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - Reclassification and Redistricting (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Baseball answer Sheets Part II 1967-1969 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Coaches Conference Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Group I- Sec 1956-1957 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Group I- Schools Correspondence 1958-1964 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Group II 1954-1955 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Group II- Central H.S. 1964 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Group II Re-class and redistricting (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Group II Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Group II- Schools Information and Correspondence 1958-1964 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - Group II Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Group II- Correspondence and Information 1958-1962 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Principals of Member Schools 1968-1969 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - 2nd School Principals Conference (Box-folder 10:13)
    - Western District Correspondence 1966-1967 (Box-folder 10:14)
    - Announcement 1959 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Coaching Clinics (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Correspondence (General) 1963-1964 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - File 1968-1969 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - Virginia State College Memoranda 1958-1960 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Virginia State College Memoranda 1963 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Virginia State college Memoranda 1961-1962 (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Virginia State College Memoranda 1957-1958 (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Miscellaneous 1953-1955 (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Miscellaneous 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Miscellaneous 1961-1962 (Box-folder 11:11)
    - Miscellaneous 1967-1968 (Box-folder 11:12)
    - Press 1965 (Box-folder 11:13)
    - Press (Correspondence) 1966-1967 (Box-folder 11:14)
    - Protest Member Schools 1955-1956 (Box-folder 11:15)
    - Protest 1965-1966 (Box-folder 11:16)
    - Sanction Meets 1968-1969 (Box-folder 11:17)
    - Public Relations (Publicity) 1957-1958 (Box-folder 11:18)
    - Publicity Releases 1965-1966 (Box-folder 11:19)
    - Schools in southern District Group (Box-folder 11:20)
    - Unassigned Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box-folder 11:21)
    - Athletic Coaches Organization Constitution (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Basketball Committee- Minutes (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Championship (State,District,Area) (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Monthly Reports (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Science Packet (Box-folder 12:5)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Speeches (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Speeches (C.D. Paige) 1959 (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Speeches (Womble) (Box-folder 12:9)
    - Womble (Box-folder 12:10)
    - Activities (Correspondence and Schedules) 1954-1964 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Agenda Coaches Meetings 1961 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - American Teachers Association Bulletin 1957-1958 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Announcements- Other Interscholastic Association (FL.) 1959-60 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Announcements and Correspondence- other Interscholastic Assns. 1960-1961 (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Announcements- Other Interscholastic Assns. 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Announcements- other Interscholastic Assns. 1962-1965 (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Appeals Committee (Box-folder 13:7A)
    - Appeal Hearing 1961-1964 (Box-folder 13:8)
    - Applications 1954-1955 (Box-folder 13:9)
    - Areas for study 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13:10)
    - Athletics-General Newsletter (Box-folder 13:11)
    - Audio-Visual Publications 1957-1959 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Audio-Visual Publications 1959-1961 (Box-folder 13:13)
    - Audio-Visual Publications 1961-1968 (Box-folder 13:14)
    - Athletic Insurance 1957-1958 (Box-folder 13:15)
    - Awards 1954-1965 (Box-folder 13:16)
    - Awards Certificates (Box-folder 13:17)
    - Baseball 1954-1958 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Baseball Correspondence 1957-1964,1967-1969 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Baseball Schedules 1962-1964,1968-1969 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Baseball, books,Pamphlets and materials 1965-1969 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Baseball Clinics 1967-68, 1968-69 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Baseball Tournament and Reports 1956 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Baseball Eligibility List- Supplementary Inmformation 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Baseball Results 1966-1967 (Box-folder 14:8)
    - Baseball Tournament 1967-1968 (Box-folder 14:9)
    - Baseball Tournament 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14:10)
    - Baseball Results Postcards 1967 (Box-folder 14:11)
    - Basketball Tournament and Minutes (Box-folder 14:12)
    - Basketball 1954-1955 (Box-folder 14:13)
    - Basketball 1954-1955 (Box-folder 14:14)
    - Basketball 1954-1955 (Box-folder 14:15)
    - Basketball Correspondence 1957-1959 (Box-folder 14:16)
    - Basketball Correspondence 1959-1963 (Box-folder 14:17)
    - Basketball Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 14:18)
    - Basketball Tournament Correpondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1956-1958 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1958-1960 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1960-1961 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1962-1963 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box-folder 15:8)
    - Basketball Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15:9)
    - Basketball Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box-folder 15:10)
    - Basketball Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box-folder 15:11)
    - Basketball Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box-folder 15:12)
    - Basketball Eligibility List 1954 (Box-folder 15:13)
    - Basketball -Girls (Correspondence,etc.) 1963 (Box-folder 15:14)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box-folder 15:15)
    - Basketball Tournament Report 1956 (Box-folder 15:16)
    - Basketball Tournament Report 1967-1968 (Box-folder 15:17)
    - Basketball Tournament Report 1957-1958 (Box-folder 15:18)
    - Basketball 1956-1958 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Basketball Tournament Champions 1961-1962 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Basketball Tournament Entry (Blanks) 1968-1969 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Official Basketball Examination 1968-1969 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Basketball Information 1962-1971 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Basketball Tournament Officials 1965-1967 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - Basketball Tournament Planning 1966-1967 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Basketball Tournament Report 1957-1958 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - Basketball Tournament Report 1958-1959 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Basketball Tournament Report 1961-1962 (Box-folder 16:10)
    - Basketball Results 1963-1965 (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Basketball Tournament Reports 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16:12)
    - Basketball Rules (Box-folder 16:13)
    - Basketball Schedules Group I and Group II 1966-1969 (Box-folder 16:14)
    - Basketball Scores-Member Schools 1957-1958, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 16:15)
    - Basketball Standings and Seasons Records 1966-1968 (Box-folder 16:16)
    - Basketball Clinic 1956 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Basketball Clinic 1958-1959 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Basketball Clinic 1961-1962 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - Basketball Clinic 1964-1966 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Basketball Clinic 1968-1969 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Basketball- Participating Schools 1960-1961 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - Basketball Tournament 1957 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Basketball Tournament Instructions 1968-1969 (Box-folder 17:8)
    - Basketball Tournament Instructions 1965-1966 (Box-folder 17:9)
    - Basketball Tournament 1967 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - Basketball 1955-1956 (Box-folder 17:11)
    - Basketball Tournament 1967 (Box-folder 17:12)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Basketball Tournament Entries (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Basketball Tournament 1955-1956 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - Tournament Bracket and Pairings 1968-1969 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - State Basketball Tourney 1961-1962 (Box-folder 18:5)
    - Basketball Tournament 1958-1962 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Basketball Tournament Correspondence 1969 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Basketball Tournament Officials (Qualified) (Box-folder 18:8)
    - Basketball Tournament -List (schools participating) 1957-1959 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - Basketball Tournament Plans (Box-folder 18:10)
    - Basketball Tournament Committee 1967-1968 (Box-folder 18:11)
    - Basketball Tournament (Bills) 1968-1969 (Box-folder 18:12)
    - V.I.A. Coaches Association 1965-1966 (Box-folder 18:13)
    - V.I.A. Coaches Association 1964-1965 (Box-folder 18:14)
    - V.I.A. Coaches 1966-1967 (Box-folder 18:15)
    - V.I.A. Coaches 1967-1968, 18:16 (Box-folder 18:16)
    - V.I.A. Coaches 1968-1969 (Box-folder 18:17)
    - Commissioner of Officials (Box-folder 18:18)
    - Correspondence coaches conference (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Correspondence Honiara (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Correspondence District Chairman Group I 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - V.I.A. Clinics Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Correspondence District 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Correspondence Activity Sponsor Chairman 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Classification Changes 1965-1967 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Clinics (sports) Correspondence 1955-1957 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Deadliest of plays 1967 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Deposit Reciepts (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Delayed Request (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Directory Information Sheets member schools (Box-folder 19:12)
    - Director of Students Activities 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19:13)
    - District Meeting Data 1957-1958 (Box-folder 19:14)
    - Drama Festival 1957-1958 (Box-folder 19:15)
    - Drama Festival 1958-1959 (Box-folder 19:16)
    - Drama Festival 1959 (Box-folder 19:17)
    - Drama Festival 1960-1961 (Box-folder 19:18)
    - Drama Festival 1961-1962 (Box-folder 19:19)
    - Drama Festival 1966-1967 (Box-folder 19:20)
    - Drama Festival 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19:21)
    - State Drama Festival (Box-folder 19:22)
    - Drama Correspondence 1964 (Box-folder 19:23)
    - Drama Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box-folder 19:24)
    - Drama Correspondence 1966-1967 (Box-folder 19:25)
    - Drama Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19:26)
    - Drama-Deadliest of Plays 1968 (Box-folder 19:27)
    - Drama Directions 1958-1959 (Box-folder 19:28)
    - Drama Entry Blanks 1960-1961 (Box-folder 19:29)
    - Dramatics Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19:30)
    - Drama Directions 1960-1962 (Box-folder 19:31)
    - Drama Directions 1962-1963 (Box-folder 19:32)
    - Drama Directions 1963-1964 (Box-folder 19:33)
    - State and District Drama Critic Judges 1961-1962 (Box-folder 19:34)
    - Drama Critic judges for district drama festivals (Box-folder 19:35)
    - Drama-List of Certified persons 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19:36)
    - Drama Workshop 1966 (Box-folder 19:37)
    - Dramatics Festivals 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Dramatics Ratings 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Dramatics Deadliest of plays for Drama 1969 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Dramatics Activities (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Dramatics Evaluation of Plays (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Dramatics List of Certified Persons (Box-folder 20:6)
    - Dramatics Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Dramatics Directions (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Dramatic Committee (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Drama Festivals 1958-1960 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Dramatic Festival 1962-1964 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Drama Festival 1965-1966 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Dramatic Minutes (Box-folder 20:13)
    - Drama-Minutes-Committee (Box-folder 20:14)
    - Drama-Printed (Box-folder 20:15)
    - Dramatics (Ratings) (Box-folder 20:16)
    - Duties Clerk Stenographer 1961-1969 (Box-folder 20:17)
    - Correspondence Eligibility 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20:18)
    - Events (Sanctioned) (Box-folder 20:19)
    - Enrollment (member schools) 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20:20)
    - Extension Course Material 1961-1963 (Box-folder 20:21)
    - Extension Course Material (Box-folder 20:22)
    - Eligibility (Box-folder 20:23)
    - Extension 1954-1957 (Box-folder 20:24)
    - Extension 1957-1960 (Box-folder 20:25)
    - Extension Classes 1958-1959 (Box-folder 20:26)
    - Florida Interscholastic Athletic Association 1952,1954 (Box-folder 20:27)
    - Florida International Athletic Association 1955 (Box-folder 20:28)
    - Florida Interscholastic Athletic Association 1956 (Box-folder 20:29)
    - Florida Interscholastic Athletic Association 1957 (Box-folder 20:30)
    - Florida Interscholastic Athletic Association 1958 (Box-folder 20:31)
    - Florida Interscholastic Athletic Association 1959 (Box-folder 20:32)
    - Florida Interscholastic Athletic Association 1965 (Box-folder 20:33)
    - Field Services Notes and Memos 1957-1962 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - Films 1955-1957 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Film Library Material 1957 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Film Library Materials 1963-1964 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Football Books, Pamphlets and materials 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Football Clinic 1957-1959 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Football Clinics 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - Football Correspondence 1958-1959 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Football Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - Football Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - Football Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Football Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Football Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Football 1956-1957 (Box-folder 21:14)
    - Football Schedules- Group I and Group II 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21:15)
    - Football Scores 1959-1960 (Box-folder 21:16)
    - Football Standings 1966 (Box-folder 21:17)
    - Forensic Activities (Box-folder 21:18)
    - Forensic 1956 (Box-folder 21:19)
    - Forensic Minutes (Box-folder 21:20)
    - General work correspondence 1956-1966 (Box-folder 21:21)
    - Girls Athletic Association Minutes 1965-1966 (Box-folder 21:22)
    - Girls Athletic Association 1965-1966 (Box-folder 21:23)
    - Girls Athletic Association 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21:24)
    - Girls Sport Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 21:25)
    - Golf Correspondence 1955-1959 (Box-folder 21:26)
    - Golf Correspondence 1963-1968 (Box-folder 21:27)
    - Golf Tournament 1967-1968 (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Guidance Program 1957-1958 (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Guidance Program 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22:3)
    - Guidelines for determining Eligibility for V.I.A. Activities (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Hampton 1964-1965 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Hardship Rules (Box-folder 22:6)
    - Hardship Rules 1967-1968 (Box-folder 22:7)
    - Hardship Cases Correspondence 1956-1966 (Box-folder 22:8)
    - High School Principals (Box-folder 22:9)
    - Industrial Club of Virginia (Box-folder 22:10)
    - Insurance 1954 (Box-folder 22:11)
    - Insurance 1955 (Box-folder 22:12)
    - Invoices 1965-1966 (Box-folder 22:13)
    - Invoices Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 22:14)
    - Invoices and Correspondence (Box-folder 22:15)
    - Invoices and Correspondence 1960-1965 (Box-folder 22:16)
    - Johnson, J.H. Correspondence (Math, Science) (Box-folder 22:17)
    - Junior, High School 1958-1960 (Box-folder 22:18)
    - Mailing List 1954-1959 (Box-folder 22:19)
    - Mailing List 1962-1965 (Box-folder 22:20)
    - Mailing List 1965-1966 (Box-folder 22:21)
    - Mailing List 1967-1968 (Box-folder 22:22)
    - Music Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 22:23)
    - Music Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 22:24)
    - Music Correspondence 1956-1957 (Box-folder 22:25)
    - Music Festivals Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 22:26)
    - Music-Music Conference of Virginia Teachers Association (Box-folder 22:27)
    - Music-Music Conference of Virginia Teachers Association 1966 (Box-folder 22:28)
    - Music-Music Conference of Virginia Teachers Association (Box-folder 22:29)
    - Music Newslettes (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Music Newsletters 1956 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Music Newsletters (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Music Newsletter (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Music Printed (Box-folder 23:5)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People 1957 (Box-folder 23:6)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People 1961 (Box-folder 23:7)
    - (National Association of Students Councils) print 1969 (Box-folder 23:8)
    - National Association of Secondary School Principals 1966-1967 (Box-folder 23:9)
    - National Federation of State Athletic Association Confirmation 1968-1969 (Box-folder 23:10)
    - National Federation of State Athletic Association Confirmation 1967 (Box-folder 23:11)
    - National High School Athletic Association 1968-1969 (Box-folder 23:12)
    - National High School Athletic Association 1969 (Box-folder 23:13)
    - National Federation Publications 1955-1963 (Box-folder 23:14)
    - National Federation Publications 1964-1966 (Box-folder 23:15)
    - Newsletters ( Student Participation Association) 1960-1961 (Box-folder 23:16)
    - Newsletter (National Association of Secondary School Principle) 1963 (Box-folder 23:17)
    - National High Athletic Association Constitution (Box-folder 23:18)
    - National High Athletic Association 1963-1965 (Box-folder 23:19)
    - National High Athletic Association-Program 1962 (Box-folder 23:20)
    - National High Athletic Association-Program 1964 (Box-folder 23:21)
    - National High athletic Association-program 1965 (Box-folder 23:22)
    - National High Athletic Association-program 1966 (Box-folder 23:23)
    - National Federation for State High School Athletic Association (Box-folder 23:24)
    - National High Athletic Association 1954-1957 (Box-folder 23:25)
    - National High Athletic Association 1963,1968 (Box-folder 23:26)
    - National High Athletic Association 1957-1962 (Box-folder 23:27)
    - National Honor Society-Minutes (Box-folder 23:28)
    - National Honor Society 1965-1969 (Box-folder 23:29)
    - National Honor Society 1966-1967 (Box-folder 23:30)
    - National Honor Society 1969 (Box-folder 23:31)
    - National Honor Society 1960 (Box-folder 24:1)
    - National Honor Society 1964-1965 (Box-folder 24:2)
    - National Honor Society 1966 (Box-folder 24:3)
    - National Honor Society Programs (Box-folder 24:4)
    - National Honor Society Conference Registration 1966 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - National Honor Society 1969 (Box-folder 24:6)
    - National Honor Society Scholarship 1969 (Box-folder 24:7)
    - National Association Secondary School Principals 1957 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - National Association Secondary School Principals 1960 (Box-folder 24:9)
    - Officials- Central Board 1961-1968 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Officials- Central Board 1957-1961 (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Officials- Central Board 1955-1956 (Box-folder 24:12)
    - Officials Charlottesville 1954-1955 (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Charlottesville bell 1955-1958 (Box-folder 24:14)
    - Officials- Culpepper Board 1962-1966 (Box-folder 24:15)
    - Officials- Danville Board 1957-1968 (Box-folder 24:16)
    - Officials- District of Columbia (Box-folder 24:17)
    - V.I.A. - Officials - Eastern Board 1956-1958 (Box-folder 24:18)
    - V.I.A. - Officials Eastern Board (Box-folder 24:19)
    - V.I.A.- Officials Eastern Board 1961-1963 (Box-folder 24:20)
    - V.I.A.-Officials Eastern Board 1964-1967 (Box-folder 24:21)
    - V.I.A.- Officials Board- Eastern Shore Athletic Officiating (Box-folder 24:22)
    - Board of Officials Eastern Shore 1968-1969 (Box-folder 25:1)
    - Officials- Frederickburg 1954-1956 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - Officials-Fredericksburg 1957-1968 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - Halifax Constitution 1967 (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Official-Halifax A.B. 1956,1968 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Board of Officials-Hampton Roads 1968-1969 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Constitution and by Laws Hampton Roads 1953,1955 (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Officials-Hampton 1955-1956 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Officials- Hampton Board 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Officials-Hampton 1958-1959 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Officials-Hampton 1960-1963 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - Officials-Hampton 1964-1966 (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Officials Boards Hampton 1967-1968 (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Board of Officials- Henderson 1968-1969 (Box-folder 25:14)
    - Officials Henderson Board 1965-1968 (Box-folder 25:15)
    - Other Meetings 1955-1957 (Box-folder 25:16)
    - Officials Advisory Committee 1966-1968 (Box-folder 25:17)
    - Officials Advisory Committee 1966-1969 (Box-folder 25:18)
    - V.I.A.- Correspondence Officials 1968-1969 (Box-folder 25:19)
    - Correspondence (Coaches- Group I & Group II) 1968 (Box-folder 25:20)
    - Officials 1954-1955 (Box-folder 25:21)
    - Officials 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25:22)
    - Board of Officials 1954-1958 (Box-folder 25:23)
    - Officials List of Officers 1957-1960 (Box-folder 25:24)
    - Memoranda to Officials 1959 (Box-folder 25:25)
    - Officials affiliated with the V.I.A. (Box-folder 26:1)
    - Correspondence 1966-1967 (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Baseball Qualified Officials 1967-1969 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Officials Baseball 1961,1966 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Officials Basketball 1957-1960 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Officials- Qualified Basketball 1967-1963 (Box-folder 26:6)
    - Officials Basketball 1964-1966 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Officials Basketball Qualified 1959-1963 (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Officials Basketball (Ratings) 1966-1967 (Box-folder 26:9)
    - Football- Qualified Officials 1966-1968 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Officials-football- list of Qualified Officials 1957-1963 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - Officials-football 1958-1964 (Box-folder 26:12)
    - Football Officials 1964-1965 (Box-folder 26:13)
    - Football Officials 1966-1969 (Box-folder 26:14)
    - Football Correspondence 1966-1967 (Box-folder 26:15)
    - Officials Football Test 1964-1969 (Box-folder 26:16)
    - V.I.A.- Harold Martin 1955-1956 (Box-folder 26:17)
    - Officials- Harold Martin Board (Box-folder 26:18)
    - Officials-Harold Martin 1960-1962 (Box-folder 26:19)
    - Officials-Harold Martin 1962-1964 (Box-folder 26:20)
    - Officials-Bluegrass Board 1962,1965 (Box-folder 26:21)
    - Board of Officials- Central 1968 (Box-folder 26:22)
    - Board of Officials Danville 1968-1969 (Box-folder 26:23)
    - Lynchburg 1955-1956 (Box-folder 26:24)
    - Officials-Lynchburg Board 1957-1958 (Box-folder 26:25)
    - Officials-Lynchburg 1959-1960 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - Officials-Lynchburg 1960-1963 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - Officials-Lynchburg 1964-1967 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - Board of Officials-Lynchburg 1968-1969 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - Officials-Martinsville-Danville 1955-1956 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - Martinsville-Danville 1955-1956 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Martinsville Board 1955-1956 (Box-folder 27:7)